{
    "id": "fb94a68f126a4296b822e635595433fc",
    "title": "During, While And In",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "55e212a8b3d04323ac89df51050c1d02",
            "title": "During, While And In",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I met them ............................. I was holidaying in Canada.",
                    "description": "While is a conjunction. We use it before a clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met them .............................. my last holiday in Canada.",
                    "description": "During is a preposition. We use it before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Janet called .................................. you were out.",
                    "description": "We use while before a clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She said that she is not responsible for anything that happened .................................. her absence.",
                    "description": "We use during before a preposition. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I fell asleep ................................ I was reading the book.",
                    "description": "We use a clause after while. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had a lot of strange experiences ............................. our vacation in America.",
                    "description": "We use a preposition after during.",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "in",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................. holidaying in Melbourne, Jerry acquired a strong Australian accent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "While",
                        "During",
                        "Since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was in Mumbai .......................... the winter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will try to meet you ............................. my trip to California.",
                    "description": "Use during before a noun/noun phrase.",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I see you for a few minutes .............................. the afternoon?",
                    "description": "Either during or in can be used to talk about the whole of the period.",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "in",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't like to answer calls ................................. I am driving.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The school was closed ............................. the whole of April.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}